(东欧)
教皇
Benedict!
真的吗
Is it true?
他们找到了那个男孩
They've found the boy?
是的
Yes.
他在这里不安全
He is not safe here.
不可能  这可是堡垒
Non sense! This is a fortress.
一切都在我们掌握之中
The full resources of the order are at our disposal.
无意冒犯您  教皇
Respectfully, Benedict.
恶魔想要这个孩子
The Devil himself wants this child.
只有一个地方对他是安全的  就是圣地
There is only one place that he's safe, that is the Sanctuary.
恶灵骑士可以带他去
The Rider must take him.
好好享受你的美酒吧  莫鲁
You do enjoy your wine, Moreau.
几天后  冬至就会过去
In a few days, the winter solstice would be pass
神示的时刻将会来临
and we'd be at hour of the prophecy.
那男孩就没有任何用处了
And the boy would be a bit no use to anyone.
等到那时  兄弟
By that time, Brother
你们都会死掉的
you'll all be dead.
谈话到此结束
This conversation is finished.
全部就位
All done!
走
Go!
娜佳
Nadya!
我可以帮助你们
I can help you!
丹尼  我可以保护你
Danny, I can protect you!
不要
No!
他们跑到哪去了
Where are they?
闭嘴
Shut up!
很好
Perfect.
这家伙是谁
Who is this guy?
蠢蛋
Stupid ass!
低头
Get down!
不管你逃多远
It doesn't matter how far you run.
总有些恶魔  你无法逃避
there are some demons you just can't escape.
我叫强尼·布雷兹
My name is Johnny Blaze.
我曾经靠骑飞车为生
I used to ride motorcycle for a living.
我曾在两万两千观众面前
I did a bare ass 360 triple back flip
无防护直接表演360度三次后空翻
in front of twenty two thousand people.
有点像飞  在视频网站上能找到
It's kind of fly, it's on youtube.
去看看吧
Check it out!
当我父亲生病后
When my dad got sick,
我干了件更疯狂的事
I did something way crazier than that.
《恶灵骑士2：复仇时刻》
看上去你需要点帮助
You look like you could use a little help?
想不想做个交易
Are you willing to make a deal?
强尼  可怜的孩子
John! That a boy!
好的  救救他
Do it! Save his life!
救救他
Do it!
没错  我和恶魔做了交易
Yah, that is right. I'm the guy who made the deal with the Devil.
我知道你们在想什么
I know what you're thinking.
这小子不看电影吗  这有用吗
Doesn't this kid watch movies, does this ever workout for me?
只能说我不擅长理智的判断
Let's just say good judgment was not exactly my forte.
我被一个远古的恶魔附身了
I was possessed by an ancient demon.
当这个恶魔出现时
In the presence of evil,
我变身为一个怪物
I change into a monster.
我狩猎恶人
And I prey on the wicked.
并且
And
我吞噬他们的灵魂
I suck out their souls.
你不会想目睹那一幕的
And you don't wanna be around when that happens.
人无完人
See, there's good and bad in all of us.
也许你不是个谋杀犯
May be you're not a murderer.
但你确实做过一些事
but you did something
不想被别人看到
you wouldn't want the record to see.
善意的谎言
A white lie.
非法下载
An illegal download.
你呢  还有你呢
What about you? And you?
我试过反抗  阻止恶魔出现
I've tried to fight. To hold it back.
但黑暗深藏在我体内
But the darkness inside me
这只会让它更强大
only gets stronger.
这就是为什么
That's why I had to run.
我逃亡了大半个地球
half way accross the world.
现在我还在逃亡
And I'm still running.
你是谁
Who are you?
我叫莫鲁
My name is Moreau.
我本该像我兄弟们那样死去
My brothers are dead as should I be.
但上帝拯救了我
If not fully intervention of God.
你是强尼·布雷兹
And you are John Blaze.
滚开
Go away!
做不到
I can't do that.
它喜欢黑暗的地方
It likes the dark places.
不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
你是恶灵骑士
You're Rider.
你可以控制那个魔鬼
This ghost that you could control it.
让它为你所用  是吧
Make it work for you, huh?
你
That you
比深处饥饿的它更强壮
were stronger than this deep hungry thing.
那个
This
恶灵
sickness.
你来这里干什么
Why are you here?
你想怎么样
What do you want from me?
我需要你的帮助
I need your help!
你需要你的灵魂
And you need your soul.
我们做个交易
So we make a deal.
你了解交易的吧  强尼
You know about making deals, don't you Johnny?
车不错
Nice bike.
这个男孩
This child...
他现在很危险
he is in danger.
他们不止要他的命
And for more than his life.
而你...
You...
要去拯救他
will save him.
我不会...
I don't...
拯救...
save...
人
people.
看看你待的地方  强尼·布雷兹
Watch what you out here Johnny Blaze?
背井离乡上万里
Thousands of miles from your place of birth.
远离你黑暗重生的地方
And your dark rebirth.
你被带到这里
You're brought here
就是为了拯救他
for this.
这个孩子
This little kid.
你凭什么相信我能找到他
What makes you think I can find him?
多年前你遇到的那个人
This man that you met
对你施加了诅咒
years ago that put the curse on you.
洛亚克
Roarke.
恶魔有很多名字
The Devil has many names.
他就是你和这个男孩的联系
He is the link that connects you to this child.
让骑士顺着本性  你会找到男孩
Let The Rider follow his stench will lead you to the boy.
你提到了交易
You said something about a deal.
我的主教们的教会
The Church of my Masters
很古老
is an ancient one.
我们会给你...
We are prepared to give to you...
世上你最渴求的东西
the one thing you want the most of this world.
帮我们带回那男孩
Bring us the boy,
我们会解除你的诅咒
and we'll lift your curse.
你好
Hello.
我...
I... uh...
我注意到你...
I notice you are... uhm,
看我
Looking at me. Yes?
我有吗
Was I ?
西装不错
Nice suit.
非常谢谢  这是...
Oh. Thank you very much. It's...
你是巴尔马吉卜赛人吗
Are you Balma Gypsi?
干嘛问这个
Why do you ask?
人们会说...
Well, what people say about...
什么
What?
听着...
Listen... uhm...
我是个商人
I am a businessman.
-我很有钱  -是吧
- I have a lot of money. - Yeah?
然后吧
And... And?
-并且...  -妈妈
- And... - Hey Mommy.
爸爸呢
Where is Daddy?
我...
I am...
-抱歉  -没事的  没事的
- Excuse me. - No, it's okay, it's okay.
我  我  我
I, I, I, yeah.
对不起
Sorry.
有人要费口舌解释一番了
Somebody's gonna have a lot of explaining to do...
我们不会一直这样下去的
We are not always gonna have to do this, okay?
我会让你过上好日子
I wanna make a life for you.
现在就不错
This is a life.
你知道我爱你胜过一切  孩子
You know I love you more than anything, child.
我也爱你  妈妈
I love you too, Mommy.
以前我总是阻止
So many times I've tried to keep
恶灵骑士附身  但今晚...
The Rider from coming out. But tonight...
我需要他
I need him.
小心
Watch out!
出什么事了
What's happened?
抓稳了
Hold on a sec...
恶灵骑士
Rider!
待在车里  锁上门
Stay in and lock the doors!
娜佳
Nadya.
不要
No!
好久不见了  亲爱的
It's been long time, Pumpkin.
卡瑞
Carrigan.
你还是这么难搞啊
See, you're still unbelievable pain in the ass.
有人在抓我和丹尼
Look, I got people after Danny and me.
放我走吧
So just let me go.
放我走
Let me go!
我就是要抓你的人
I am the people after you.
不要
No!
-别碰他  -闪开
- Don't touch him! - Get off!
真厉害
Oh, unbelievable!
依旧这么顽强
Still the fighter.
卡瑞
Carrigan.
怎么了
Yes?
求你了
Please.
他是我的儿子
He is my son.
我知道呀
I know.
不过不是我的儿子
But he's not mine!
你应该知道会有这么一天
Part of you had to know that might end up like this!
杀了它
Oh, kill it!
不要
No.
天啊  不要
Oh God, no!
好饿
Hungry.
搞定他
Set those now.
别看他
Don't look at him.
不要  不要
No! No!
搞定
Get some.
快走
Move ,now!
带他上车
Get him in the car!
上车
Get in!
丹尼
Danny!
你醒了
Oh, You have awake.
挺搞笑  因为...
It's funny, 'cause...
你走进来的时候...我...
when you walked in... I, uhh...
我以为我还在做梦
I thought, I was still dreaming.
你出现幻觉了吗
You have hallucinate?
没有  女士  我没产生幻觉
No, No madam. I am not hallucinating.
我和你调情来着
Look, I'm flirting with you.
你太美了
You're beautiful.
好吧...
Okay...
吗啡  我要吗啡...
Morphine. To I Morphine...
你有吗啡吗
You got any Morphine?
没有...  你已经注射过了
No no morphine..... You already have.
麻醉剂呢...
Narcotics...
安定呢...  你有什么
Valium... what do you got?
你的伤口...
Your wounds...
-你很奇怪  先生  -是的
- You're very weird, Mister. - Yes!
-你醒后警察想跟你谈谈  -不
- The police, I want to talk to you when you wake up... - no.
-我会告诉他们你醒了  -不
- I'll tell them you awake. - No.
求你了
Please.
我没事  让我走
I'm fine. Let me go.
不行  你需要休息
No, you should take some rest.
出来
Take a piss.
卡瑞
Carrigan.
我拿到你要的了
I got your package
但是替我办事的人涨价了
but the guards doing business for me just went up.
我不明白
I don't understand.
你不懂什么
What's not you understand?
我想要更多
I want more.
懂了不
You understand that?
我们可是有约定的  卡瑞
We have an agreement, Carrigan!
随意更改约定
Changing the define terms of agreement
可不是我们的风格
is something we just don't do.
你让我去抓个孩子
You told me to get a kid.
没问题
Not a problem!
这活我以前也干过
I've done that for people before.
我跟他妈有过一腿
And, I have a history whose his bitch of mom.
所以找我是最好不过的了
So there's no better guy for the job.
但你没告诉我
But what you didn't tell me?
这会像恐怖电影似的
Is that I be walking into middle goddamn horror movie!
这好笑吗
How is this funny to you?
昨晚我有三个手下成了火柴杆儿
Three of my guys get turned into match stick last night.
因为一个摩托车手...头上着火的家伙
By a dude on the motorcycle... with his head on fire.
-你说什么  -你听到了
- Come again? - You heard me.
我也见过世面  古怪的  糟糕的
I've seen things, weird things, bad things.
但昨晚那样的...
But that thing last night...
不...不...不...不
No...no... no.....no.
让男孩接电话
Put the boy on the phone.
说话
Talk!
丹尼
Danny?
你能听见吧
Do you hear me?
你要仔细听我说  丹尼
I want you to listen very closely. Listen to me, Danny.
这是什么玩意儿
What the hell was that?
把这孩子看做电脑
Think of the child was sort of computer.
电脑你懂吧
You know computers, right?
我只是上传了一个程序
I just upload it a little program.
一个防火墙
A firewall.
我们那个摩托车手朋友
Our friend on the motorcycle
就察觉不到他...无法追踪了
won't be able to sense him now... to track him.
当然了
Of course.
他仍有可能找到你  所以...
He is still maybe able to find you. So...
我建议你  继续跑吧
I suggest to you, keep moving.
喂
Hello.
谁派你来的
Who sent you to find me?
是魔鬼吗
Is it the Devil?
魔鬼还在人间行走吗
The Devil walks among man?
是不是恶魔  回答我
Does the Devil? Own you answer me.
那个孩子
The kid.
丹尼
Danny.
他是你儿子吗
He is your son?
子弹伤不了你  你有魔鬼附身
Bullets can't hurt you anymore, and you work the Demon?
但他们已经这么做了
But, I think they've gonna do.
我凭什么相信你
Tell me why I can trust you!
你不能
You can't!
但如果我找不到你的儿子
But if I don't find your son?
我就死定了
I just assumed be dead.
所以如果你想开枪
So if you wanna pull that trigger.
那就来吧
Do it!
来吧
Please.
你昨晚追踪到我们
You tracked us last night.
你还能这么做吗
Can you do it again?
之前我能感觉到他
I could feel him before.
本来能  但之后就消失了
I could sense him, and then nothing.
不不  他没死  只是...
No, no. He's not dead! He's just...
被封印了
blocked.
但你知道些什么
But you know something?
走吧
Let's go.
我们理理清楚...
Yeah okay, look, let me just get something straight...
那家伙绑架了丹尼...
The guy who kidnapped Danny...
想杀了你...
And try to kill you and blow me up...
用榴弹炸死我
with grenades.
你们俩以前是情侣吗
You two were like boyfriend and girlfriend?
卡瑞曾是个枪手...毒品贩子  雇佣军
Carrigan was a gunrunner... A drug dealer and a mercenary...
我什么都不在乎  只想出去
I didn't care about any of that. I just searched to get out.
好吧  那丹尼是...
Right, ok! So Danny...is...
是什么  卡瑞的儿子吗
Danny what? Is Carrigan's son?
不是
No.
你遇到恶魔时...
When you met the seducer...
-他答应你什么了吗  -是
- He offered you something? - Yeah...
救活我父亲
My father's life.
很意外  他撒了谎
Shocker. He lied.
而我  是为了我自己
For me... it was only myself.
这本来是卡瑞惹的麻烦
It was supposed to be big screwed in Carrigan,
但是他执迷不悟
but he want bad...
我死里逃生
I maded it out of third floor into hell.
口吐鲜血
I was choking on my own blood.
我知道难逃一死
I knew! I was gonna die.
死神触手可及
I could feel it.
然后它发现了我...
And that's when he found me...
你看起来需要帮助
You look like you could use a little help?
洛亚克
Roarke.
他答应把疼痛带走
He promised to take the pain away.
拯救我的生命
To save my life.
但是他提出了交换条件
But he asked for something in return.
你儿子
Your son?
也许你永远不会理解
Maybe you can never understand.
不...我理解
No... I get it.
你是魔鬼的代孕妈妈
You are the Devil's baby mama.
难怪莫鲁那么想要...
I guess that explains why Moreau wants...
丹尼  非常急切
Danny. So bad.
莫鲁
Moreau?
对  黑皮法语酒精牧师混球
Yeah... Black-French-alcoholic-priest-kind-of-dick.
怎么  认识他
Why? You know him?
他要帮我们  我没让
He tried to help us. I didn't let him.
以后我们一块决定
We were both gonna work on our decision making.
我们去哪里
Where are you headed?
找个故人
To someone I know.
他为卡瑞做那些不法勾当
He does Carrigan's dirty work.
他知道他的下落
He'll know where to find him.
为什么恶魔要以人形行走世间
Why does the Devil walk on earth in human form anyway?
我不知道
I have no idea.
也许他自己也不知道
Maybe he doesn't know either.
也许他只是...
Maybe he's just...
从一个躯体移到另一个...
passes on from body to body.
一直如此下去...
Down through history...
等待最完美的肉身
Waiting for the perfect fit.
但是  有一件事我肯定...
But, I know one thing...
在人间
On earth.
他很虚弱
he's weak!
他的力量被限制
His powers are limited.
他需要帮凶
He needs emissaries
来为虎作伥
to do his dirty work.
所以他找到他们或创造他们
So he finds them or makes them.
用他强大无比的力量
Using his greatest power.
这力量就是...
The power of...
交易
The Deal.
我能开窗透透气吗
Can I open a window?
你以为你有资格讲话吗
Do you think you can just talk?
你妈以为她有资格讲话
You know, your mom thought that she could just talk.
直到我巴掌扇在你吉普赛人的脸上
Until I get doing your gypsy face.
卡瑞  救我出去
Carrigan get me out of here!
在地狱里好好享受吧
Enjoy yourself in the twinkie's hell.
救我出去
Get me out of here!
老大
Boss.
过来
Come here.
再跑一次试试...你会...
You try that again... you will return...
什么
What?
会讲英语吗
You speak English?
会  伙计  怎么回事
Yeah, Dude! What happened?
那是你的车吗
Is that your Van?
对啊
Oh... yeah.
-能用吗  -当然
- Is it in run? - Yeah.
搞定后  继续前进
When we get over... go ahead.
骑士就要出来了
The Rider's going to come out.
骑士出来后
When he does
任何挡路者必死
he'll destroy whoever he's got it coming.
娜佳
Nadya...
这种事...
This thing...
没有缘由...
There is no reason...
或者意识
or conscious.
只有饥饿
Just hunger.
在它眼里
And his eyes.
你和卡瑞没什么不同
You're not different than Carrigan...
但和他们又很不一样
you're different than any of them.
我不惧怕你
I'm not afraid of you.
是吗
Yeah?
你应该怕我
You should be.
就是那个家伙
That's the guy?
像游轮上的打工仔
Looks like he works on a cruise ship.
我应该后悔带你来吗
Am I gonna regret taking you?
是的
Yeah.
有可能
Probably.
每分钱都要数
Count every dollar!
这帮蠢蛋别想讹我
I don't want these idiots robbing me.
每个人都想诈我
Everyone's robbing me!
真让我蛋疼
It makes my balls hurt!
你好  西尔
Hello, Vasil.
好久不见  娜佳  还是很漂亮
Long time Nadya. You look good.
住口  住口
Shut up! Shut up!
他和卡瑞通过话
He's been talking to Carrigan.
分别在几天前  几小时前
Last couple of days and few hours ago.
强尼
John.
你和卡瑞通过话
You talked to Carrigan?
我和很多人都通过话
I've talked to a lot of people!
我这有东西治你的发抖  朋友
Hey, I've got what your need for your shakes, my friend.
卡瑞肯定没告诉你是什么
Carrigan musn't told you about that thing.
我昨晚杀了他的人
I kill his men last night... huh?
知道吗
Yeah...
那东西在我身体里
That thing is inside me.
瞧  你是个人渣
See, you are bad man!
那东西  恶灵骑士
And this thing, The Rider,
他以人渣为食  现在他饿了
he feeds on them and he is hunger!
他饿了很多年  所以我发抖
His hunger has been years and that's why I am shaking!
因为现在  你和他之间
Cause right now, the only sanity
唯一理智的就是我了
between you and The Rider, is me.
他就要...他就要...
He's just... he's just...
他在门内爬行  在门内爬行
He's creeping at the door! He's creeping at the door!
如果你不好好合作
Who might, if you don't tell me what I wanna know.
我就会放他出来
I am gonna let him out!
我很想挺你
I want to stand with you.
你会连渣都不剩  明白吗
You won't be anything left! Do you understand?!
明白吗
Do you understand?!
-点头或摇头  懂不懂  -懂
- Shake your head, yes or no? - Yes.
好  好样的
Good. Good girl.
卡瑞在哪里
Where is Carrigan?
我不想杀你  别逼我杀你
I'm not to kill you, I can't kill you now.
告诉我或者让我吃了你的灵魂
You will tell me or I will eat your stinking soul!
在采石场  为了更多的枪
The quarry! For more guns ,
更多的人手  他要组成一支部队
more men. He's putting together goddamn army.
我知道那地方
I know the place.
你不会把这次谈话泄露给任何人吧
You are not gonna exhibit this conversation to anyone, are you?
不会
No.
回答得很好
Oh yeah! All right. That's a good answer.
-好样的  -强尼
- Good girl! - John!
我们撤  我们撤
We gotta go! We gotta go!
FGM148标枪火箭弹
FGM 148 Javelin,
目标锁定  弹无虚发
lock on fire and forget.
美式掩体破坏弹
American bunker buster.
两级爆发
Two stage detonation.
第一级产生超真空
The first creates super vacuum.
榨取空气中的氧气
It sucks the oxygen from the air.
-第二...  -我知道怎么样
- The next... - I know what it does.
给我四个  加额外的弹头
Give me four of them with extra heads.
你要对付多少人
How many men you go up against?
就一个
Just one.
丹尼
Danny!
妈妈
Mom!
还好吗
Are you okay?
都怪我  都怪我
I am so sorry, I am so sorry.
我来救你出去
I am gonna get you out of here.
我想我脚踝折了
I think my ankle is broken.
来  忍着点
Come on, hold on.
不好
Oh, no.
我们走  抓紧我
Come on. Hold on to me!
好戏开场了
Show time.
什么玩意
What is it?
管他呢
I don't care.
把那玩意递给我  快点
Give me that thing. Give it to me, come on.
好耶
yeah!
真不赖啊
That was awesome.
快上弹  上弹
Hey! Would you reload? Reload!
扔手榴弹炸他
Throw the grenade!
给我
Give me that!
快点
Hey hurry!
抱歉  痛不痛啊
I'm sorry did that hurt?
看起来很痛啊
You look like it did.
我们快跑
Come on, let's go.
快点
Hurry!
抱歉  痛不痛啊
Sorry does it hurt?
看起来很痛啊
It's look like it does.
你还等什么  杀我  杀我啊
What are you waiting for? Do it! Do it!
他追来了
He's coming.
放开我
Let me go.
够了
Enough!
放...开...她
Let... her... go!
就这样发生了
So, that happened.
给你
There you go.
有只蜜蜂
It was a bee.
我想  已经跑了
I thought, it was gone.
蛰了你的脸一下
Sting your face.
感觉好点了吗
What, you feeling better?
你的脚都好了
Your legs all heal huh?
像是自然痊愈的
Like all by it self?
很奇怪
That's weird.
我妈呢
Where's my mom?
她给卡车加油去了
She's gassing up the truck.
我知道现在说这个
I know that it's
有点尴尬
little awkward.
我是说和你们在一起
I mean rolling with you guys.
我是说等一切结束之后
I mean after everything.
伙计
Dude,
你比我妈前男友们要酷多了
you way cooler than guy she usually hangs up.
下一步做什么
So, what's next?
莫鲁认为几天后危险就会过去
Moreau seems to think the danger pass in a few days.
我们只要把丹尼送到某个安全的地方
And we just get Danny in someplace safe.
圣所可以保护我们
The holy place where people can protect us
我们可以去那里  那是我们的目的地
and we can ride it down. That's where we headed.
好
Ok.
我已经联系好了莫鲁
I've already contacted Moreau.
他在路上和我们会合
He's gonna catch up with us on the road.
我们要加快速度
We gotta move fast.
一旦他们想追捕我们
Cause if they want to hunt us.
就不会善罢甘休
they're not done.
当然我还有些个人恩怨
Of course I have some personal issues.
要找他们解决
I kinda like to get fixed.
还没结束呢  卡瑞
You're not done, Carrigan!
你要把娜佳的儿子带给我
You are to bring me Nadya's son.
我期待你能完成给你的任务
I do expect you to fulfill your obligation.
抱歉  蠢货
S...S...S... sorry, jackass.
可我要死了
But I am dead.
真麻烦
Inconvenient.
你把我怎么了
What you do to me?
给了你第二次机会
Gave you a second chance.
你现在和活着差不多
You a little less than alive now.
甚至更强
But also more.
瞧...我给了你力量
See... I have given you power.
腐蚀的力量
The power of decay
以及黑暗的力量
of darkness.
我要那孩子  卡瑞
I want that boy, Carrigan!
不要再讲什么借口了
Now you've got no excuses.
昨晚的那个机器
The machine last night.
-怎么  -你让它变形了
- Yeah. - You made it changed.
那是他的能力  他操作的东西随他而变
That how it works. Whatever he rides, changes with him.
那他坐的士怎么办
And what if you took the taxi?
这  我...我不清楚  不清楚
Ugh, I... I don't know, I don't know.
过山车或者滑雪缆车或...
A rollercoaster or ski lift at tow or...
你燃烧的时候要是想撒尿怎么办
Hey! What if you have to pee when you're on fire?
太棒了
Ugh, it's awesome,
就像喷火器  你知道  就像...
it's like a flame thrower. You know, it's like...
当你改变  变成他时
When you change, when you him,
感觉好吗
does it feel good?
有时候是
Sometimes.
什么意思  很糟吗
What is that mean? All just bad?
不
No.
我们拥有的力量  来自黑暗世界
This power that we have, comes from the dark place.
但不是我们的本来面目
But it's not who we are.
也永远不会是
Never will be.
我们可以用它做好事
And we can use it to the good.
去助人为乐
To help people.
就像我在帮助你和你妈
Like I am helping you and your mom.
我知道你为什么要帮我们
I know why are you helping us.
她说你想摆脱他
She says you wanna get rid of it.
我却摆脱不了
I can never do that.
你们好
Bonjour!
娜佳  希望你别再开枪打我了
Hey Nadya, I hope you have finished shooting at me.
想找点乐子吗
Hey! You wanna have some fun?
坐稳了
You gotta hang on.
太诡异了
It's so weird.
这就是莫鲁的幸福之地
So this is it Moreau's happy place.
我是说这些人能解除我的诅咒吗
I mean these guys gonna lift my curse?
他们甚至连鞋都没有
They didn't even have shoes.
桑格
Sunger.
毋须害怕  是神指引你们来此
You mustn't be afraid. It was God that let you here.
什么事
What's up?
我知道  有点太拘谨
I know! A little too uptight.
等了解他们后就感觉不赖了
But not so bad when you get to know them.
走吧
Go on.
他们会好好照顾你们的
They will take good care of you.
你们俩去哪里
What about you two?
我们去去就来
We will join you later.
我们之间还有些事要完成
We have some business to complete between us.
我向你保证过  强尼
I made a promise to you, John.
他为什么不能和我们一起来
Why can't he come with us?
不
No!
丹尼  丹尼
Danny. Danny.
在这里你很安全
You're safe here.
我们成功了
We made it.
现在唯一能伤害你和你妈妈的
The only thing that can hurt you and your mom now
是我
is me.
我要确保那永远不会发生
I need to make sure that will never happen.
一切都会好的
It will be all right.
我保证
I promise.
-好吧  -我们走
- Whatever. - Come on.
你确定吗
Are you sure about this?
走吧
Come on.
我们去哪
Where are we going?
去我最喜欢的地方
To my favorite world.
说起这些混球们最了解的事
If they ask one thing these sons of bitches know out.
那就是葡萄酒了
It's wine.
这瓶拍出了五万欧
This bottle was fetch fifty thousand Euros at an auction.
-莫鲁  -爽
- Moreau. - Oh. Yeah.
那是什么
What is it?
-这是  -我说的是我身体里的那东西
- It's... - It's thing inside of me.
在我们动手之前  我想知道它是什么
I would like to know before we commence.
扎拉朵思  曾是个天使
Zarados, was an angel.
是正义之灵
Spirit of justice.
他被派来保护人类世界
Sent to protect the world of men.
但是  却被欺骗  被俘获
But, he was tricked, captured.
最终拖入了地狱
Brought down to hell.
他渐渐堕落
Corrupted.
变得疯狂
Driven insane.
他保护无辜的人使命
His mission to protect the innocent
堕落成了惩罚恶者欲望
was perverted into a lust to punish the guilty.
它变成了
It became...
复仇之魂
the spirit of vengeance.
那个天使呢
What about the angel?
正义之灵
Spirit justice.
他还活着吗
He's alive in there?
还在某个地方
Somewhere?
可能吧
It could be.
你能感觉到他吗
Do you feel him?
不能
No.
开心点吧  伙计
Cheer up, my man.
很快你就能得到自由
Soon you'll be free.
这一瓶
This bottle.
这瓶已经超过两千年
This one is over two thousand years old.
我看上它有段时间了
I've had my eye on it for while.
这一切都结束的时候
When this is over
我们一起来喝
we will share it too.
你有什么没告诉我
There is something else.
你的诅咒很不容易消除
This thing that your curse done to you, is not easily undone.
你会有生命危险  比死亡更严重
You risk death, worse than death.
你必须忏悔
You must confess,
那件最难以启齿的事
the one thing that is most difficult for you to talk about.
我父亲
My dad,
我当初不是为了他
I didn't do it for him.
是他为我做的交易
He made the deal for me.
我没办法就这样失去他
I couldn't let him go.
我太自私了
I was selfish.
他已经做好了死亡的准备
He was ready to die.
他知道是时候了
He knew it was his time.
我却以为我可以改变它
And I thought I could change that.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
这是上帝的羔羊
This is the Lamb of God.
它可以带走世间的罪恶
That takes away all the sin from the world.
降福于所有被选中的人
Happy all those that are called to receive Him.
你还没有准备好见主吗
You say, that you're not ready to receive Him?
是的  还没有
No, I'm not.
好的  这样就可以了
Ok. That's good enough.
耶稣的躯体
The body of Christ.
阿门
Amen.
你带着这块面包有段时间了
You, you've been carrying this bread around for while.
愿上帝带你得到永生
May God lead you into the eternal life.
强尼  如果今天
That is John, if today,
确实是你最后...
is in fact, your last...
现在你要去的地方  我不能跟随
Where you go now, I can not follow.
你准备好了吗
Are you ready?
有人吗
Hello?
要动手就快点  混蛋
Make it quick, you asshole!
做交易吧
Make the deal!
莫鲁
Moreau!
你成功了
You did it!
莫鲁
Moreau!
成功了
It worked!
不
No!
放开我
Let me go!
放开
Leave me!
-松手  -你们想干什么
- Get off me! - What are you doing?
放开我
Let me go!
你想干什么
What are you doing?
完成必须做的事
What will be done.
明天就是预言日了
The day of prophecy is tomorrow.
在危险过去之前要看好那个男孩
You'd like to hold the boy until the danger passes.
只要这个男孩还存在  莫鲁
The danger will not pass, Moreau.
危险就不会过去
As long as the boy exists.
力量会一直在他体内
The power always be inside of him.
你骗了我
You lied to me.
你居然骗我
这个孩子必须被摧毁
This child must be destroyed.
你怀孕的时候就该阻止这一切发生
You might have protested while the child has been conceived.
现在已经太晚了
Now, it is too late.
完事之前先把他们关起来
Take them away until the thing is done.
丹尼的灵魂可以被拯救
Danny's soul can still be saved.
那个孩子  他是上帝的子女
That boy. He's one of the God's children.
不  他不是
No! He's not.
帅气吧
Pretty neat ,huh?
安息吧  兄弟
Peace, brother.
爽
Damn.
见到我高兴不
Bet you happy to see me.
这是丹尼做的吗
Did Danny do this?
不是
No.
有人来了  在他们...
Somebody got here, before they could...
在他们杀掉他之前
before they could kill him.
四处都找不到他
There's no sign of him.
无论这是谁干的  都想让他活着
Whoever did this wanted him to be alive.
我想我们都知道谁干的  莫鲁
I think we all have pretty good idea who that would be, Moreau.
他现在和洛亚克在一起
Yes, so now he is with Roarke.
类似你曾经那样的守护者是吗
Some protectors you turned out to be.
洛亚克到底想干什么
What exactly just Roarke have in mind for the enemy?
他在计划什么
What is his plan for his size?
难道是为上大学存钱吗
Is he putting money away for college, or what?
明天就是预言日
It is the day of prophecy.
就像丹尼受孕的日子
As was the day Danny was conceived.
孩子必须长到13岁
The child must be in his 13th year,
才能在冬至的破晓实施仪式
before the rite can be performed on the dawn of the new winter.
仪式
The rite.
洛亚克将那孩子用作容器
Roarke fathered the boy as a vessel,
装载他力量的容器
as a container for his power.
仪式可以把他的精髓
The ritual will transform his essence,
他的灵魂  导入那孩子体内
his soul, into the boy.
丹尼就不复存在了
There will be no more Danny.
-只剩下洛亚克  -不
- Only Roarke. - No!
你为什么没有早告诉我们  莫鲁
Why the hell you didn't tell us this, Moreau?!
明明是你和洛亚克做了交易  你们俩都是
Hey, you're the one who made the deal with Roarke! Both of you!
我可没有
Something I would never do.
好吧  预言日
All right, the prophecy.
你说仪式必须在黎明时举行
You said, it had to happen at the dawn of new day.
很好  也许我们还有时间
That's good. Maybe there's still time.
你知道洛亚克会把他带到哪
Do you know where Roarke has him?
我知道
I think so, yes.
然后呢  难道你想装英雄吗
Now what, so now you want to play hero?
你已经达到目的了
You got what you wanted.
是  没错
Yes, I did.
谢谢你  信守承诺
Thank you, for holding up your end of the bargain.
不用客气
You're welcome.
如果我人生的最后一天
If I could spend the last day of my life
可以摆脱从地狱而来的诅咒
as free man without a curse from hell hanging over my head?
我当然求之不得
Yeah, I'll take that.
但我向丹尼保证过  他是安全的
But, I promised Danny, he'd be safe.
如果我现在离开  和魔鬼也没什么两样
And by walking away now, I'm just trading one demon for another.
我们动身吧
So let's go.
(乌兹卡哥克登  土耳其)
-我办事还用担心吗  -不要碰我
- Was there really doubt? - Don't touch me!
贴得有点近了吧  哥们
Kind of get a bit close, aren't we?
你知道我都经历了什么吗
Do you have any idea, what I had to go through?
就为了抓住这个小混账
To get this little turd.
计划又与你的异教徒集会无关
Look, the plan is don't align
要到明天破晓才能进行
for your little pagan party until daybreak tomorrow.
所以不要烦我  我已经提前完成了
So get off my ass, cause I'd say, I'm ahead of schedule.
丹尼
Danny?
你知道我是谁吗
Do you know who I am?
我想你妈妈一定和你说了不少
I'm sure your mother told you a lot of things about me.
你的脸怎么回事
What's the matter with your face?
乌兹卡哥克登  离天堂最远的地方
Uzak Gokten, the furthest point from heaven.
仪式将在那里举行
That is where the ritual is to take place,
正如预言那样
according to the prophecy of course.
当然
Of course.
没有了恶灵骑士  我们想战胜洛亚克很难
Without The Rider, we stand very little chance against Roarke.
-我以为你应该有信心  -我有
- I thought, you're supposed to have faith? - I do.
但是同时  我们也需要武器
But also, I think we should have weapons.
枪与葡萄酒
Guns and wine.
调皮的神父
Naughty priests.
我又开始喜欢你了  莫鲁
I'm starting to like you again Moreau.
你想知道为什么我会这样
You wanted to know, why I look this way?
就想想...
Think of...
喷火器
the flame thrower.
好笑吗
Is that funny?
好吧  我这个形状的喷火器确实搞笑
The flame thrower made out of the paper my shape.
所有的力量
All that power.
想用的话  就要点燃自己
Try to use it, you burn up.
我的这幅躯干  很弱小
This body, I'm living in, it's weak.
人类的躯干
Human.
它在枯竭
It's dying.
无法让我随心所欲
It was never made to do the things that I can do.
但是你  你并不全是人类
But you. You're only part human.
你可以掌控我给你的力量
You will rule the power that I have inside of you.
像子承父业一样
Like father like son.
但是这个实体
But this corporeal form
可以支配力量  但不伤及自身
can wield the power, without burning itself up.
帮你休息一下
To help you relax.
够他一直睡到仪式了
That will keep him sedated until the ceremony.
那些都是谁
Who are they?
政客  杀手  掌权者
Politicians, murderers, people of influence.
都是恶魔的手下
The Devil's soldiers.
他们从世界各地而来
They've traveled from all over the world,
为亲眼目睹新帝王的诞生
to witness of the uniting of The New King.
新帝王
The New King.
别搞笑了
Please.
如果洛亚克成功  就会有一个新形态
If Roarke succeeds, we have a new form.
比以往都要强大的形态
One more powerful than is ever known.
他的阴霾将笼罩世间
And his shadow will fall upon the earth.
二十度角五个  三十度九个  里面更多
Twenty five, thirty nine. More inside.
仪式已经开始
The ritual has already begun.
丹尼的灵魂会在破晓永远的消失
Danny's soul will be lost forever at the break of dawn.
那时的洛亚克最虚弱
This is when Roarke is at his weakest.
娜佳
Nadya?
你还好吗
You all right?
我犯过很多错误  布雷兹
I've made a lot of mistakes, Blaze.
但是
But Danny,
生下丹尼
Danny is the one,
是我这辈子
the one good thing,
做过最对的选择
I ever did.
如果是那样的话  我们最好
That being the case, we had better
确保他不要被变成反基督徒
make sure he doesn't turn out to be the anti-Christ.
-时间不多了  -计划是什么
- Not much time? - What's the plan?
你去抢走那男孩  逃跑  不要停
I need you go and grab the boy, you run, and you don't stop.
你呢
What about you?
我
Me?
我从正面攻击
I'm going through the front.
真不赖
Not bad.
无比荣幸
This won't be my bigger honor, sour.
强尼·布雷兹
Johnny Blaze.
上帝保佑我
Bona me.
出发
Go.
你们好
Bonjour.
尝尝这个吧
Check this one out!
好酒浪费了真可惜
What a waste of good wine.
窝火
Mad!
感觉真好
I feel good.
能听到我吗
Can you listen to me?
我不该舍弃那力量  我知道
I should never of gone rid of the power, I know that now.
他想让你的灵魂消失
He's gonna erase you Danny.
莫鲁
Moreau.
我依然可以看见光明
I can still see the light.
真恶心
That's gross.
你没有力量了  布雷兹
You have no power Blaze!
在我面前你不过是蝼蚁
You're nothing but an insect.
甚至更糟  成为魔鬼的食物
For the worst, food for the meals of hell.
你想来观看吗
Oh, you wanna watch?
有其父必有其子
The apple doesn't rot far from the tree.
丹尼
Danny.
这不是你
This is not who you are.
永远也不会是
It never will be.
我们两个能力相同
My powers and yours are the same.
你是这么说的  对吧
That's what you said. Right?
爸爸  像子承父业
Dad? Like father like son.
来吧
Do it.
不
No.
过来
Come here.
我从来没怕过你
I was never afraid of you.
车祸
Road kill.
你...
You...
是我做过最差的交易
were the worst fucking deal, I ever made.
滚回去吧
Go home!
丹尼
Danny.
天使
The Angel.
莫鲁说过骑士曾经是天使
Moreau says The Rider was an Angel...
变疯的天使
that went crazy.
我可以感觉到他
I can feel him
天使
The Angel.
我能感到他的存在
I can feel him.
丹尼
Danny!
Danny.
我们赢了吗
Did we win?
我想是的
I'm gonna say yes.
我们赢了
Hell yes.
我是强尼·布雷兹
My name is Johnny Blaze.
我就是恶灵骑士
I'm the Ghost Rider.